<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">EncourageMe</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">Splash</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="whatsNewTitle">Welcome</string>
    <string name="whatsNewText">Welcome to EncourageMe!\n Set the start and end time to control the time of day you will receive messages. Set the frequency at which you would like to receive messages between these hours. Press Set Encoureme and you will begin receiving encouragements. You can edit or delete these settings at any time.</string>
	
    <string name="frequency_prompt">Select frequency of encouragements</string>
 
    <string-array name="freq_array">
        <item>Once a day</item>
        <item>Every 12 hours</item>
        <item>Every 8 hours</item>
        <item>Every 4 hours</item>
        <item>Every 2 hours</item>
        <item>Every hour</item>
        <item>Every 30 minutes</item>
        <item>Every minute</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="messages">
        <item>Trust yourself, if you can\'t why should anyone else.</item>
        <item>You can\'t always get what you want, but if you try sometimes you just might find you get what you need. -The Rolling Stones</item>
        <item>Have convictions, apathy is the adversary of action.</item>
        <item>The key is to keep company only with people who uplift you, whose presence calls forth your best. -Epicetus</item>
        <item>Follow your passions and you will never have regrets.</item>
        <item>Above all else be a person that you regret.</item>
        <item>Look and listen, you will learn.</item>
        <item>Go confidently in the directions of your dreams! -Henry David Thoreau</item>
        <item>If you’re going through hell, keep going. -Winston Churchill</item>
        <item>However good you are, you can be better.</item>
        <item>Never be afraid to fail, eventually you will succeed.</item>
        <item>Why do we fall? So we might learn to pick ourselves up. -Batman Begins</item>
        <item>Nothing worth doing is easy.</item>
        <item>You are capable of greatness, believe in yourself and work hard.</item>
        <item>If life seems overwhelming, take a deep breath, a step back, and remember how lucky you are to have what you have.</item>
        <item>Finish what you start, you will like yourself more for it.</item>
        <item>To try and then fail is better than not trying at all.</item>
        <item>You have the potential to tap into the well of human strength within you.</item>
        <item>The world is full of infinite possibilities.</item>
        <item>I know of no more encouraging fact than the unquestionable ability of man to elevate his life by conscious endeavor. -Henry David Thoreau</item>
        <item>Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work. -Aristotle</item>
        <item>You\'re a winner.</item>
        <item>A creative man is motivated by the desire to achieve, not by the desire to beat others. -Ayn Rand</item>
        <item>Impress yourself.</item>
        <item>Live the life you have imagined. -Henry David Thoreau</item>
        <item>Instead of giving myself reasons why I can’t, I give myself reasons why I can.</item>
        <item>Smile. Let everyone know that today, you\'re a lot stronger than you were yesterday.</item>
        <item>No matter how good or bad you think your life is, wake up each day and be thankful. Someone somewhere else is fighting to survive.</item>
        <item>Life is short. Think positive, you\'re worth it!</item>
        <item>Today will never come again. Be a blessing. Be a friend. Encourage someone. Take time to care. Let your words heal and not wound.</item>
        <item>Big jobs usually go to the men who prove their ability to outgrow small ones. -Ralph Waldo Emerson</item>
        <item>You don\'t stop laughing because you grow old, you grow old because you stop laughing.</item>
        <item>Don\'t cry from a mistake. Learn from it and move on. Stop blaming yourself for things you have no control over.</item>
        <item>Whether you think you can or whether you think you can\'t, you\'re right. -Henry Ford</item>
        <item>To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment. -Ralph Waldo Emerson</item>
        <item>Trust yourself. You know more than you think you do. -Benjamin Spock</item>
        <item>When we feel good about ourselves and embrace our talents and resources, we have taken the first steps toward realizing our full potential. -Gillian Stokes</item>
        <item>If you want to dismiss a negative thought, the only way to do so is to think of something positive and constructive. -Emmet Fox </item>
        <item>When you feel like giving up, like calling it quits, just try one more time, do that little bit more. -Catherine Pulsifer </item>
        <item>The ablest man I ever met is the man you think you are. -Franklin Roosevelt</item>
        <item>Don\'t look into the past because you\'ve already been there. Focus on the future since that\'s where you\'re going.</item>
        <item>Always stay true to yourself because there are very few people who will always be true to you.</item>
        <item>I find hope in the darkest of days, and focus in the brightest. I do not judge the universe. -Dalai Lama</item>
        <item>Forgive those who have hurt you in the past. But more than this, forgive yourself for allowing them to hurt you.</item>
        <item>Do not underestimate yourself by comparing yourself with others. You only need to make yourself happy.</item>
        <item>Everything is possible; your dreams, your ideas, your vision. Never let anyone tell you that you can\'t.</item>
        <item>It\'s not about how you look on the outside, it\'s how you feel on the inside that matters. Show others your true self.</item>
        <item>Setbacks are temporary as long as you don’t give up. -Kevin Ngo</item>
        <item>You\'ve got this. Just take a deep breath, close your eyes for a moment and loosen up your muscles. There is nothing you can\'t do as long as you stay calm and breathe.</item>
        <item>Don\'t let anyone hold you back. If you put your mind to it you can achieve greatness in your life.</item>
        <item>Nothing is impossible. You can become anything you want in life. Stay focused, remain positive and you will accomplish great things.</item>
        <item>Do just once what others say you can’t do and you will never pay attention to their limitations again. -James R. Cook</item>
        <item>We are not all given the same opportunities in life but that does not mean we can not all achieve greatness. Never give up on yourself and you will be unstoppable.</item>
        <item>Satisfaction does not come with achievement, but with effort. Full effort is full victory. -Mahatma Gandhi</item>
        <item>Take the attitude of a student, never be too big to ask questions, never know too much to learn something new. -Og Mandino</item>
        <item>Don\'t quack like a duck.. soar like an eagle. -Ken Blanchard</item>
        <item>To succeed in life in today\'s world, you must have the will and tenacity to finish the job. -Chin-Ning Chu</item>
        <item>An ambitious horse will never return to its old stable. -Chinese Proverbs</item>
        <item>I’d rather be a failure at something I love than a success at something I hate. -George Burns</item>
        <item>We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars. -Oscar Wilde</item>
        <item>High expectations are the key to everything. -Sam Walton</item>
        <item>Quality is not an act, it is a habit. -Aristotle</item>
        <item>If I’m going to do something, I do it spectacularly or I don’t do it at all. -Prince Alwaleed Bin Talal Alsaud</item>
        <item>The men who have succeeded are men who have chosen one line and stuck to it. -Andrew Carnegie</item>
        <item>Encourage your people to be committed to a project rather than just be involved in it. -Richard Pratt</item>
        <item>The only limit to your impact is your imagination and commitment. -Anthony Robbins</item>
        <item>Talent is cheaper than table salt. What separates the talented individual from the successful one is a lot of hard work. -Stephen King</item>
        <item>I quickly learned that if I kept at it and plowed right through the rejections I would eventually get somebody to buy my wares. -Charles Schwab</item>
        <item>Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. -Jeffrey Immelt</item>
        <item>A clear vision, backed by definite plans, gives you a tremendous feeling of confidence and personal power. -Brian Tracy</item>
        <item>You have to have doubts. I have collaborators I work with. I listen and then I decide. That\'s how it works. -Giorgio Armani</item>
        <item>Greatness is not a function of circumstance. Greatness, it turns out, is largely a matter of conscious choice, and discipline. -Jim Collins</item>
        <item>We are not animals. We are not a product of what has happened to us in our past. We have the power of choice. -Stephen Covey</item>
        <item>You will either step forward into growth or you will step back into safety. -Abraham Maslow</item>
        <item>Success is not for the timid. It is for those who seek guidance, make decisions, and take decisive action. -Jose Silva</item>
        <item>Develop success from failures. Discouragement and failure are two of the surest stepping stones to success. -Dale Carnegie</item>
        <item>What we think determines what happens to us, so if we want to change our lives, we need to stretch our minds. -Wayne Dyer</item>
        <item>Along with a strong belief in your own inner voice, you also need laser-like focus combined with unwavering determination. -Larry Flynt</item>
        <item>The greatest glory in living lies not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall. -Nelson Mandela</item>
        <item>The world is more malleable than you think and it\'s waiting for you to hammer it into shape. -Bono</item>
        <item>Hard work, dedication and perseverance will overcome almost any prejudice and open almost any door. -John H. Johnson</item>
        <item>A happy life consists not in the absence, but in the mastery of hardships. -Helen Keller</item>
        <item>I\'ve always worked very, very hard, and the harder I worked, the luckier I got. -Alan Bond</item>
        <item>Action may not always bring happiness, but there is no happiness without action. -Benjamin Disraeli</item>
        <item>Doing what you love is the cornerstone of having abundance in your life. -Wayne Dyer</item>
        <item>You\'ve got to love what you do to really make things happen. -Philip Green</item>
        <item>For a man to conquer himself is the first and noblest of all victories. -Plato</item>
        <item>In essence, if we want to direct our lives, we must take control of our consistent actions. It’s not what we do once in a while that shapes our lives, but what we do consistently. -Tony Robins</item>
        <item>A happy man is too satisfied with the present to dwell too much on the future. -Albert Einstein</item>
        <item>Even a happy life cannot be without a measure of darkness, and the word happy would lose its meaning if it were not balanced by sadness. -Carl Jung</item>
        <item>The winner is the chef who takes the same ingredients as everyone else and produces the best results. -Edward de Bono</item>
        <item>Innovation distinguishes between a leader and a follower. -Steve Jobs</item>
        <item>Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever. -Mahatma Gandhi</item>
        <item>It\'s not where you start or where you finish. It is the distance between the two. -David Icke</item>
        <item>Make at least one definite move daily toward your goal. -Bruce Lee</item>
        <item>When you set goals, something inside of you starts saying, "Let\'s go, let\'s go," and ceilings start to move up. -Zig Ziglar</item>
        <item>Positive things happen to positive people. -Sarah Beeny</item>
        <item>We are what we think. All that we are arises with our thoughts. With our thoughts we make the world. -Gautama Buddha</item>
        <item>To me every hour of the day and night is an unspeakably perfect miracle. -Walter Chrysler</item>
        <item>When you live your life with an appreciation of coincidences and their meanings, you connect with the underlying field of infinite possibilities. -Deepak Chopra</item>
        <item>You\'re a wizard Harry!</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>